Hello it's me and welcome to a new video here on my channel Celine Knox. Today I'm going to show you some really fancy outfits. Some PVC clubbing outfits so to say. I have something in black and red and in pink. And I'm going to tell you a secret about the brand later. But first naughty thoughts outfit one. Here we go.
This is the thinner vinyl top and high waist panty and there are also gloves which I'm going to get into now.
These are one size by the way and you're supposed to scrunch them a bit at the wrist.
Let's see.
Oh yeah.
So scrunch them at the wrist like this.
So they're a bit loose fit.
how it's supposed to be and this is the full outfit and I love it because it's black and
because it's really cool I also love the cut here in the back because I think it makes a really nice
booty also everything is size adjustable all the straps are size adjustable the lacing here is
adjustable I crisscrossed it here in the front but you can also do it straight or just do a bow here
maybe and there is a wire like a long underbust wire running here and also which I love
removable padding in the bra and everything is lined so really really high quality you also have
the naughty thoughts signature where is it I can't feel it with the gloves let me see it yeah
Naughty Thoughts signature in gold here in the back. I introduced this fashion from Naughty Thoughts
to you as clubbing outfits for like the fittish scene. I think you would pass every door bitch
at fittish parties with this outfit but actually it's pole dance wear. How fun is that and how cool
is that? Imagine wearing something like this for pole dance. All the other outfits I'm going to
show you. Really cool and I think really unique stuff and they look great on pole.
You can check out the Instagram of Naughty Thoughts. She's doing pole dance
herself and she looks so awesome. It's really cool. But yeah definitely not only
for pole dancing. That's what I love about it. And I asked her why PVC for
pole dance and I thought she was like it's another variant of latex with all
without all the hassle of latex like it's easier to maintain and to wear and
to dress but it still looks cool and has this nice shine and also fun fact vinyl
PVC really really sticks to the pole I tried it myself so that's really cool
I'm going to change into the next outfit it's going to be a lot of pink PVC and
also mesh parts so see you in a bit wait stop I'm not done there still things
missing outfit number two it's pink and I hate how much I love pink with blue
wear damn it so good so again vinyl thinner vinyl under boob top and a thong this time
so an outfit before it was the high waist penny now it's a thong but this one's also
available in black and everything is mixed and it's the back side
the garter belt and the schrock are this kind of really stretchy see-through mesh and I think
they complete the look I think I would feel undressed without the schrock and the garter belt
because uh only the thong and the top are really yeah not much still you would pass every doorman
of a fetish party with this outfit. Not only pole wear. And I did a mix and match here because
the straps for the garter belt here are actually interchangeable. You can use this one, the
wider one, or you can use this one and you can just change it here. But I added the small one
underneath because I think it's a nice look and it looks cool with the extra strap here. I love it.
I just love the whole outfit. I also love the under boob cut which I think looks awesome. So
a really extravagant outfit for every kind of party. Probably summer party because
it is really lofty and you would freeze in winter or for a Celtic pole and again
you have the gold name tags here and also again padding here in the bra which
is really cool as a woman I can say that padding in bras is nice also for sports
and lining everywhere again so it's really comfortable it doesn't get too sweaty it
doesn't stick too much to your skin although it will stick to the pole
and I'm just really happy with this I love these outfits so much I think they're so cool
so thank you Naughty Thoughts for this collaboration and I also have a discount
code for you guys if you want to check out the outfits I'll link it down below
I have one last outfit in red, really bold color, less vinyl than the other two outfits but you'll see for yourself. It's red and it is again really badass. It's the XXX rated see-through bodysuit and XXX rated garter or suspender.
and it's one piece the bodysuit with the cut out here in the shoulders and really high leg
then I added the um panty and the garter belt which is really a cool cool item itself it is
again um size adjustable here with the straps and you can detach the cute little chain here in the
middle and also tighten the criss-crossed strips here. Strips? I don't know what to
call them in English. In Germany we would say Kordel, which is a really unsexy word.
But the outfit is really sexy. And it came with pasties. So you can wear them underneath
or, naughty thoughts, there's maybe a bikini top. Since I'm here on YouTube I opted
for the same version and made a small latex bundle top to wear under it. I
think it looks cool together. I want to show you the backside because the backside is
also really nice with the black garters here and it's another outfit I just adore.
Again maybe not the first thing you imagine when you think about pole dance
but it looks bomb on pictures and videos. I've seen a lot of videos with it and
really cool. Also they have a male outfit which I obviously can't show you but I'm
going to show you a picture now because I think it's really unique design also
for male dancers or pole dancers. Also for a male fetish party outfit so check
it out. And please tell me which of the outfits you like most. I really can't
decide. Oh yeah and before I forget there is another feature here in the bodysuit
which I didn't do before because then the lip gloss would be smeared all over
the bodysuit. There is basically an integrated mask. Wait I'm going to put it on for a sec.
So again as I said I'm wearing lip gloss. It's not the wisest idea to talk then because then the whole gloss would be in the fabric. But it's also cool, really cool for pictures and also I really like the fabric.
It's a bit delicate. You have to be a bit aware of handling it with care because it's really thin mesh.
But otherwise I just love these outfits.
Would you wear it for party? The outfit one, two or three?
I'm definitely going to wear the black outfit to a fetish party in summer.
Maybe I'll even do pole dance one day with that stuff. I'm not sure yet because I'm not that good yet.
So yeah, check out everything I put in the description text and give this video a thumbs up.